Guide to the Football Game Film Collection, 1934-2007 UA.13.01.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Football Game Films
  - NC State, 1988 November 12
    - Duke vs. NC State: Kick, 1988 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1533)
  - North Carolina, 1988 November 19
    Duke win, score: 35-29
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 1, 1988 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 28, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1534)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 2, 1988 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 28, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1535)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 1, 1988 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 28, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1536)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 2, 1988 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 28, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1537)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Kick, 1988 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 28, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1538)
  - South Carolina, 1989 September 02
    Duke loss, score: 21-27
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Defense 1, 1989 September 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1539)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Defense 2, 1989 September 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1540)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 1, 1989 September 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1541)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 2, 1989 September 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1542)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Kick, 1989 September 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1543)
  - Northwestern, 1989 September 09
    Duke win, score: 41-31
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Defense 1, 1989 September 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1544)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Defense 2, 1989 September 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1545)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Offense 1, 1989 September 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1546)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Offense 2, 1989 September 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1547)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Kick, 1989 September 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1548)
  - Tennessee, 1989 September 16
    Duke loss, score: 6-28
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Defense 1, 1989 September 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1549)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Defense 2, 1989 September 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1550)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Offense 1, 1989 September 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1551)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Offense 2, 1989 September 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1552)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Kick, 1989 September 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1553)
  - Virginia, 1989 September 23
    Duke loss, score: 28-49
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 1, 1989 September 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 33, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1554)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 2, 1989 September 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 33, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1555)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 1, 1989 September 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 33, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1556)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 2, 1989 September 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 33, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1557)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Kick, 1989 September 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 33, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1558)
  - Clemson, 1989 September 30
    Duke win, score: 21-17
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 1, 1989 September 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1564)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 2, 1989 September 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1565)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Offense 1, 1989 September 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1566)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Offense 2, 1989 September 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1567)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Kick, 1989 September 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 33, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1568)
  - Army, 1989 October 07
    - Duke vs. Army: Defense 1, 1989 October 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1559)
    - Duke vs. Army: Defense 2, 1989 October 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1560)
    - Duke vs. Army: Offense 1, 1989 October 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1561)
    - Duke vs. Army: Offense 2, 1989 October 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1562)
    - Duke vs. Army: Kick, 1989 October 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1563)
  - Maryland, 1989 October 21
    Duke win, score: 46-25
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Defense 1, 1989 October 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1569)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Defense 2, 1989 October 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1570)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Offense 1, 1989 October 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1571)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Offense 2, 1989 October 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1572)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Kick, 1989 October 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1573)
  - Georgia Tech, 1989 October 28
    Duke win, score: 30-19
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Kick, 1989 October 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1574)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 1, 1989 October 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1575)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 2, 1989 October 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1576)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 1, 1989 October 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1577)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 2, 1989 October 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1578)
  - Wake Forest, 1989 November 04
    Duke win, score: 52-35
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 1, 1989 November 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1579)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 2, 1989 November 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1580)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Kick, 1989 November 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 30, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1581)
  - NC State, 1989 November 18
    Duke win, score: 35-26
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 1, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1582)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 2, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1583)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 1, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1584)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 2, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1585)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Kick, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1586)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 1, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 33, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1592)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 2, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 33, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1593)
  - North Carolina, 1989 November 18
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 1, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1587)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 2, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1588)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 1, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1589)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 2, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1590)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Kick, 1989 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 32, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1591)
  - Texas Tech, 1989 December 14 and 1989 December 28
    Duke loss, score: 21-49; All-American Bowl
    - Duke vs. Texas Tech: Defense 1, 1989 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1594)
    - Duke vs. Texas Tech: Defense 2, 1989 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1595)
    - Duke vs. Texas Tech: Offense 1, 1989 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1596)
    - Duke vs. Texas Tech: Offense 2, 1989 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1597)
    - Duke vs. Texas Tech: Kick, 1989 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 31, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1598)
    - Duke vs. Texas Tech: Unknown game coverage: "The Road to Birmingham", 1989 December 14; 2" video (Box 136)
  - South Carolina, 1990 September 01
    Duke loss, score: 10-21
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: First Quarter, 1990 September 01; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0033)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Second Quarter, 1990 September 01; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0034)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Third Quarter, 1990 September 01; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0035)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1990 September 01; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0036)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 1 Tite Line, 1990 September 01; U-matic (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0001)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 2 Tite Line, 1990 September 01; U-matic (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0002)
  - Virginia, 1990 September 22
    Duke loss, score: 0-59
    - Duke vs. Virginia: First Quarter, 1990 September 22; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0037)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Second Quarter, 1990 September 22; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0038)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Third Quarter, 1990 September 22; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0039)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Fourth Quarter, 1990 September 22; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0040)
  - Clemson, 1990 September 29
    - Duke vs. Clemson: First Quarter, 1990 September 29; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0041)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Second Quarter, 1990 September 29; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0042)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Third Quarter, 1990 September 29; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0043)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Fourth Quarter, 1990 September 29; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0044)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 1 Tite Line, 1990 September 29; U-matic (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0003)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 2 Tite Line, 1990 September 29; U-matic (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0004)
  - Army, 1990 October 06
    Duke win, score: 17-16
    - Duke vs. Army: First Quarter, 1990 October 06; BetaCamSP (Box 47, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0045)
    - Duke vs. Army: Second Quarter, 1990 October 06; BetaCamSP (Box 47, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0046)
    - Duke vs. Army: Third Quarter, 1990 October 06; BetaCamSP (Box 47, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0047)
    - Duke vs. Army: Fourth Quarter, 1990 October 06; BetaCamSP (Box 47, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0048)
  - Western Carolina, 1990 October 13
    Duke win, score: 49-18
    - Duke vs. Western Carolina: First Quarter, 1990 October 13; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0049)
    - Duke vs. Western Carolina: Second Quarter, 1990 October 13; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0050)
    - Duke vs. Western Carolina: Third Quarter, 1990 October 13; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0051)
    - Duke vs. Western Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1990 October 13; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0052)
    - Duke vs. Western Carolina: 1 Tite Line, 1990 October 13; U-matic (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0005)
    - Duke vs. Western Carolina: 1 Tite Line, 1990 October 13; U-matic (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0006)
  - Maryland, 1990 October 20
    Duke loss, score: 20-23
    - Duke vs. Maryland: First Quarter, 1990 October 20; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0053)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Second Quarter, 1990 October 20; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0054)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Third Quarter, 1990 October 20; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0055)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Fourth Quarter, 1990 October 20; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0056)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 1 Tite Line, 1990 October 20; U-matic (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0007)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 2 Tite Line, 1990 October 20; U-matic (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0008)
  - Georgia Tech, 1990 October 27
    Duke loss, score: 31-48
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Sideline, 1990 October 27; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0057)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: First Quarter, 1990 October 27; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0058)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Second Quarter, 1990 October 27; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0059)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Third Quarter, 1990 October 27; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0060)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Fourth Quarter, 1990 October 27; BetaCamSP (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0061)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 1 Tite Line, 1990 October 27; U-matic (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0009)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 1 Tite Line, continued, 1990 October 27; U-matic (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0010)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 2 Tite Line, 1990 October 27; U-matic (Box 35, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0011)
  - Wake Forest, 1990 November 03
    Duke win, score: 57-20
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: First Quarter, 1990 November 03; BetaCamSP (Box 47, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0062)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Second Quarter, 1990 November 03; BetaCamSP (Box 47, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0063)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Third Quarter, 1990 November 03; BetaCamSP (Box 47, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0064)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Fourth Quarter, 1990 November 03; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0065)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 1 Tite Line, 1990 November 03; U-matic (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0012)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 2 Tite Line, 1990 November 03; U-matic (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0013)
  - NC State, 1990 November 10
    Duke loss, score: 0-16
    - Duke vs. NC State: First Quarter, 1990 November 10; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0066)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Second Quarter, 1990 November 10; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0067)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Third Quarter, 1990 November 10; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0068)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Fourth Quarter, 1990 November 10; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0069)
  - North Carolina, 1990 November 17
    Duke loss, score: 22-24
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: First Quarter, 1990 November 17; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0070)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter, 1990 November 17; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0071)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Third Quarter, 1990 November 17; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0072)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1990 November 17; BetaCamSP (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0073)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: End zone 1, 1990 November 17; U-matic (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0014)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: End zone 2, 1990 November 17; U-matic (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0015)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: End Zone 3, 1990 November 17; U-matic (Box 34, Video-cassette UA13010004-Umatic-0016)
  - South Carolina, 1991 September 07
    Duke T, score: 24-24
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 1 Sideline, 1991 September 07; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0074)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 2 Sideline, 1991 September 07; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0075)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 3 Sideline, 1991 September 07; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0076)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 4 Sideline, 1991 September 07; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0077)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: End zone 1, 1991 September 07; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0078)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 2 End zone, 1991 September 07; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0079)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: End Zone 3, 1991 September 07; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0080)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: End Zone 4, 1991 September 07; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0081)
  - Rutgers, 1991 September 14
    Duke win, score: 42-22
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: First Quarter, 1991 September 14; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0082)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: Second Quarter, 1991 September 14; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0083)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: Third Quarter, 1991 September 14; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0084)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: Fourth Quarter, 1991 September 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0085)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: End zone 1, 1991 September 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0086)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: 2 End zone, 1991 September 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0087)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: End Zone 3, 1991 September 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0088)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: End Zone 4, 1991 September 14; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0089)
  - Colgate, 1991 September 21
    Duke win, score: 42-14
  - Virginia, 1991 September 28
    Duke loss, score: 3-34
    - Duke vs. Virginia: First Quarter, 1991 September 28; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0098)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Second Quarter, 1991 September 28; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0099)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Third Quarter, 1991 September 28; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0100)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Fourth Quarter, 1991 September 28; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0101)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: End zone 1, 1991 September 28; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0102)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 2 End zone, 1991 September 28; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0103)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: End Zone 3, 1991 September 28; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0104)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: End Zone 4, 1991 September 28; BetaCamSP (Box 38, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0105)
  - Vanderbilt, 1991 October 05
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: First Quarter, 1991 October 05; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0106)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Second Quarter, 1991 October 05; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0107)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Third Quarter, 1991 October 05; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0108)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Fourth Quarter, 1991 October 05; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0109)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: End zone 1, 1991 October 05; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0110)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: 2 End zone, 1991 October 05; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0111)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: End Zone 3, 1991 October 05; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0112)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: End Zone 4, 1991 October 05; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0113)
  - Maryland, 1991 October 26
    - Duke vs. Maryland: End zone 1, 1991 October 26; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0114)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 2 End zone, 1991 October 26; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0115)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: End Zone 3, 1991 October 26; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0116)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: End Zone 4, 1991 October 26; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0117)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 1 Sideline, 1991 October 26; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0118)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 2 Sideline, 1991 October 26; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0119)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 3 Sideline, 1991 October 26; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0120)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 4 Sideline, 1991 October 26; BetaCamSP (Box 48, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0121)
  - Georgia Tech, 1991 November 02
    Duke loss, score: 6-17
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 1 Sideline, 1991 November 02; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0122)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 2 Sideline, 1991 November 02; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0123)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 3 Sideline, 1991 November 02; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0124)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 4 Sideline, 1991 November 02; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0125)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: End zone 1, 1991 November 02; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0126)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 2 End zone, 1991 November 02; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0127)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: End Zone 3, 1991 November 02; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0128)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: End Zone 4, 1991 November 02; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0129)
  - Wake Forest, 1991 November 09
    Duke loss, score: 14-31
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: First Quarter, 1991 November 09; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0130)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Second Quarter, 1991 November 09; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0131)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Third Quarter, 1991 November 09; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0132)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Fourth Quarter, 1991 November 09; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0133)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: End zone 1, 1991 November 09; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0134)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 2 End zone, 1991 November 09; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0135)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: End Zone 3, 1991 November 09; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0136)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: End Zone 4, 1991 November 09; BetaCamSP (Box 39, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0137)
  - NC State, 1991 November 16
    Duke loss, score: 31-32
    - Duke vs. NC State: First Quarter, 1991 November 16; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0138)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Second Quarter, 1991 November 16; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0139)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Third Quarter, 1991 November 16; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0140)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Fourth Quarter, 1991 November 16; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0141)
    - Duke vs. NC State: End zone 1, 1991 November 16; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0142)
    - Duke vs. NC State: 2 End zone, 1991 November 16; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0143)
    - Duke vs. NC State: End Zone 3, 1991 November 16; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0144)
    - Duke vs. NC State: End Zone 4, 1991 November 16; BetaCamSP (Box 37, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0145)
  - North Carolina, 1991 November 23
    Duke loss, score: 14-47
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 1 Sideline, 1991 November 23; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0146)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 2 Sideline, 1991 November 23; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0147)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: 3 Sideline, 1991 November 23; BetaCamSP (Box 36, Video-cassette UA13010004-Bcam-0148)